emiratesgroupcareers.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Emirates Group Careers

#### 1\. Information collection and use

Emirates Group ('Emirates') includes any and all of the following entities and/or brands: Emirates, dnata, dnata World Travel, Emirates Skycargo, Skywards, Emirates Holidays, Arabian Adventures, Emirates Hotels & Resorts, Congress Solutions International, and their associated brands and/or companies from time to time. A list is available upon request from: Corporate Communications, PO Box 686, Dubai, United Arab Emirates. We are responsible for the processing of any personal information you provide to emiratesgroupcareers.com (the ‘Website’) and we are notified where required in each country under the relevant data protection legislation of that country. We take our responsibilities regarding the protection of personal information very seriously. This policy explains how we use personal information that we may obtain about you. By using our Website you consent to this use.

#### 2\. Why do we need your personal information?

When you use services provided on this Website you will be asked to provide certain personal information in order to apply or register for jobs, or to join the company. We will store this information and hold it on computers or otherwise. We will use this information in the following ways:

  * To process your job application(s);
  * To register you with our Website and administer our Website services where you have registered to receive these. You can unsubscribe from these services at any time (see Choice/Opt-out below);
  * To answer any queries which you may send to us by e-mail;
  * For crime prevention and detection; and
  * In order to send out e-mail job alerts according to your stated preferences

#### 3\. How do we use your personal information?

Information you provide or that is obtained by us will be used by us to enable us to review, develop and improve the services which we offer and provide you and other users and applicants (via mail, email telephone or otherwise) with information about job opportunities and information queries which you request.

#### 4\. Who do we share your information with?

We may give information about you as follows:

  * to other companies and/or brands in Emirates Group for the purposes of progressing your employment application;
  * if we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do so;

If you choose not to provide certain personal information we request, you will still be able to visit our Website but you may be unable to access certain options or services.

#### 5\. Security

We will take appropriate steps to protect the personal information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features to safeguard the privacy of your personal information.

#### 6\. Cookies

  1. #### a. What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's computer and is stored on your device's hard drive. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our Website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our service.

Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Many websites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows.

  2. #### b. How do we use cookies and our types of cookies?

Our Website uses four different types of cookies. We use cookies to understand how users interact with our Website, to measure the effectiveness of advertising on third party sites and to provide a seamless service when you use our Website.

We also use third party cookie providers to assist us in providing you with a better service and to help us analyse our customer behaviour. All third parties are under strict confidentiality obligations and are restricted from using any information for their own business or other purposes. If you visit a page on one of our websites one or more of the cookie types set out below may be generated.

#### Log-in cookies

When you log-in to the Website we generate cookies that inform us when you log-in and log-out. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and if you are allowed access to a particular service.

We also use cookies to keep information such as your language and other preferences. All cookies are temporary as they are session cookies. Once the session is closed or expired, so are the cookies.

When you opt-in to us saving your account information these cookies instruct us to pre-populate the User ID field with your email address when you return to the log-in page.

#### Site performance cookies

We may generate cookies to assist with site performance. Some examples are:

    * Balancing the load of users between our different servers to maximise user experience.
    * Using third party cookies to enable you to input information on one page and move to another page while our Website remembers your information, so that there is a seamless service (e.g. using log-in only pages).
    * Remembering video streaming speeds which are compatible with your browser.

#### Anonymous tracking cookies:

When you visit our Website an anonymous tracking cookie is generated by a third party web analytics software provider to inform us whether or not you have visited our site before. This allows us to track how many individual unique users we have, and how often they visit our Website. Unless you are signed into the Website, these cookies cannot be used to identify individuals; they are used for statistical purposes only.

#### Third party cookies

In some cases we use third party advertising cookies which allow us to understand and improve the effectiveness of our advertising on both our own and third party websites.

If you’ve previously received a cookie from Facebook because you either have an account or have visited [facebook.com](https://facebook.com/ "opens in a new window"), your browser sends Facebook information about this cookie when you visit a site like emiratesgroupcareers.com which displays the Facebook “Like” button.

  3. #### c. How to reject cookies?

**By using our Website you are consenting to the use of cookies as described herein.**

However, all modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can set your devices to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these means that certain personalised features cannot then be provided to you and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the Website's features. Each browser is different, so check the ‘help’, 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. You can also visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. This site includes details on how to delete cookies from your computer as well as more general information about cookies.

#### 7\. Links

Our Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of websites not operated by us or an entity in the ‘Emirates Group’. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our Website.

#### 8\. Correction/updating of personal information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove your personal information provided to us.

#### 9\. Choice / Opt-out(BSG/IT to check/insert links)

If you no longer wish to receive job alerts you may opt-out of receiving these communications by unchecking the “Send me an email notification whenever a new position matching my profile is posted (job posting notification)” preference under your Account Options.

#### 10\. Access to your personal information

You have the right to see personal information we keep about you. We will endeavour to provide the information you require within a reasonable time. There may be a small monetary charge for some requests, depending on the information requested. 

#### 11\. Transfer of your personal information

Some parties that process or store personal information may be located in jurisdictions outside your country of residence. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in these jurisdictions and, as a result, foreign governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through the laws in these countries.

#### 12\. Notification of changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of an email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

#### 13\. What is recruitment fraud?

It has come to our attention that various people and organisations unrelated to the Emirates Group are sending emails or otherwise contacting individuals offering fraudulent  employment opportunities in the Emirates Group. These people and organisations may request personal information or money from you in order to progress the application. We would therefore advise that you never provide your bank account or credit card details as part of a job application.

During our recruitment process you would always meet in person with an Emirates Group employee or representative for an interview before any formal offer of employment is made.

Emirates Group will never ask for money transfers or payment of any kind from job applicants., and will never ask for advance payment from you towards travel expenses or visas/work permits if your application is successful. **Be wary of anyone who asks you for money in order to take up a job opportunity with Emirates Group as this offer will be fraudulent.**

If you receive an email that appears to be from Emirates that instructs you to send replies to an email address other than one ending with “@emirates.com” or from “emiratesgroupcareers@invalidemail.com” please treat it as fraudulent and notify us through the recruitment help desk so we can take appropriate action as quickly as possible.
